FER WICKER

0426 404 077 fer.wicker@gmail.com 12 Ewell St, Balmain NSW 2041

Visa: Permanent Resident

Profile

I have several years' experience working in customer service in various industries both face to face and in call centres. I firmly believe in providing an outstanding experience every time.

I have well developed verbal and written communication skills with a cheerful disposition and a professional, friendly telephone manner. I work well under pressure and as part of a team. I am a fast learner and an avid reader.

Languages

Fluent English

Fluent Spanish

Skills

Excellent verbal and written communication skills

Professional phone manner

Ability to work under pressure in a fast paced environment

Attention to detail

Time management

Work well as part of a team

Creative thinking

Positive attitude

Friendly disposition

Motivated and fast learner

Social media management

Photography

Software

Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel and PowerPoint

Proficient in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign

Proficient in Squarespace

Competent in Wordpress

Work History

Customer Care | Travellers Autobarn Sydney | July 2020 - March 2020

Answer calls and emails from customers on the road. Provide friendly and effective assistance and advice. Liaise with branches, repairers and suppliers. Followed up multiple cases at a time to resolution.

- Provided consistently excellent customer service.
- Worked in a high volume and fast paced environment.
- Quick creative thinking to find solutions
- Created and maintained rapport with customers and repairers

Marketing Coordinator/Graphic Designer | Coco Cubano Sydney | November 2015 - December 2019

Produce and coordinate all design and marketing material for a group of 11 restaurants. Collaborate with each franchisee to meet their local marketing needs. Encouraged a shift of focus to customer experience. Follow up complaints and feedback trends with the operations manager and restaurant managers.

- Developed and implemented complaints management
- · Shifted focus to customer experience

Digital Assistant | **Designate Group** Sydney | July - November 2015

Short term project work. Proofread annual reports for major companies. Populated web versions of reports to exact specifications. Worked on several projects at the same time and managed time to meet deadlines.

- · Worked with close attention to detail
- Worked to deadline in a fast paced environment

Reservations Assistant | **Keystone Group** Sydney | April 2013 - May 2015

Received high volume of calls. Replied to email and social media enquiries and complaints. Followed procedures and kept up to date records. Provided knowledgeable and friendly answers. (continues on page 2)

Education

Diploma of Graphic Design

TAFE - Design Centre Enmore Completed June 2015

Statement of Attainment in Illustrating Books for Children

TAFE - Design Centre Enmore Completed May 2017

Creative Writing Course

Centre for Continuing Education Completed September 2014

Digital Photography Course

Escuela Activa de Fotografía Completed March 2012

Interests

Hiking/bush walking

Travel

Photography

Reading

Writing

Yoga

Painting

Digital illustration

Fun Fact

In 2017 I illustrated and designed a childrens book called Pointy Pembleton. The book was crowdfunded for self publishing and exceeded the funding target by 80%. Pointy Pembleton Visits the Dog Park was published in September 2017.

Referees

Alison Piro Corporate Services Manager | Coco Cubano 0414 435 442

Sam Cundall Customer Care Team Leader | Travellers Autobarn 0408 973 687

Work Experience (continued)

Reservations Assistant | **Keystone Group (continued)** Sydney | April 2013 - May 2015

Liaised with restaurants regarding customer needs to ensure an outstanding experience. Worked effectively as part of a team.

- Worked in a high volume call centre
- Built and maintained rapport with guests
- Resolved complaints and provided solutions

Shift Supervisor/Bartender | Chimichurri Bar & Grill Sydney | August 2012 - March 2013

Communicated with other team members to ensure all customers had a great experience. Maintained high standards of service and quality. Built and maintained rapport with regular customers. Trained new front of house staff.

- Provided excellent service in a fast paced restaurant
- Resolved complaints in a calm and friendly manner

Sales/Graphic Designer | Tempo Design Mexico City | January 2012 - July 2012

Worked with each customer to meet their needs. Managed multiple projects to deadline. Liaised with printers and other suppliers. Exceeded sales targets.

- Managed multiple tasks effectively
- Face to face customer service and sales

Customer Service Agent | High Marketing and Telemarketing Mexico City | June 2010 - January 2012

Client was a major soda company in Mexico. Received a high volume of calls from consumers, stores and suppliers and liaised between them. Kept detailed records according to procedure. Followed up each individual case to completion.

- Provided excellent customer service consistently
- Worked as part of a team in a fast paced environment

Volunteer Experience

Greyhound Rescue | Sydney | April 2015 - January 2017

Worked as part of a team managing Greyhound Rescue's active social media. Devised and executed fundraising ideas. Generated artwork for merchandise. Designed collateral for print. Attended events where we helped educate the public, answer questions and explain the adoption processes. Photographed dogs at the kennels to promote adoption.

- · Face to face contact with the public at events
- Social media management

Elephant Nature Park | Chiang Mai, Thailand | July 2015

One week volunteer experience. Contributed to daily keeping of rescued elephants, including cleaning, feeding and park maintenance. Learned about conservation and rehabilitation of elephants in Thailand and the work of Lek Chailert.

- Hands-on and physically demanding
- Exciting and enriching learning experience